Guide to the Fordham W. R. Petersen, Jr., Class of 1957, School of Art and Architecture, Yale University, Photographs Documenting Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Fordham W. R. Petersen Jr., Class of 1957, School of Art and Architecture, Yale University, photographs documenting Yale
1957-1957
RU 641
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The materials consist of photographs of Yale and New Haven, Connecticut taken by Fordham W. R. Petersen, Yale School of Art and Architecture, Class of 1957 (non-graduate).
Petersen, Fordham W. R.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of Yale and New Haven, Connecticut taken by Fordham W. R. Petersen, Yale School of Art and Architecture, Class of 1957 (non-graduate).
College buildings; New Haven (Conn.) -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Petersen, Fordham W. R.; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings
- Photographs, Series I
  - East Rock, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grove Street Cemetery headstones, 1956
  - 77 Prospect Street, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale Art Gallery patio, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Orpheus" by Carl Milles in Art Gallery, 1956
  - Harkness Tower from Art Gallery patio, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - View from top of Drama Theater, 1956
  - 6 Hillhouse -Sheffield Biological Laboratory, 1956
  - Snapshots, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)